So you must be devastated
about your divorce.
(Beverley:)Oh, not at all. But I am a bit distressed
to be in a vehicle...
(Beverley:)...that's not subjected
to regular maintenance.
(Penny:)Come on, I mean, you're not upset
that your marriage is over?
(Beverley:)Well, initially I felt something akin
to grief and perhaps anger...
(Beverley:)...but that's the natural reaction
of the limbic system...
(Beverley:)...to being betrayed
by a loathsome son of a bitch.
(Penny:)-Sure. Sure.
-Thankfully, my shock was mitigated...
(Beverley:)...by the fact that I haven't had
intercourse with him in eight years.
(Penny:)-Eight years?
-Oh, that's nothing.
(Beverley:)I've been responsible
for my own orgasms since 1982.
(Penny:)Yikes.
[BEVERLY CHUCKLING]
Wha--? What's so funny?
(Beverley:)That's exactly what I say
during orgasms: Yikes.
(Penny:)I could use a drink.
You wanna stop for a drink?
(Beverley:)-Oh, I don't drink.
-I do. I'll teach you.